And that's a good catch taken by Ramakrishnan
at long off First wicket fall
so welcome back once again ICS Lomar
presents Brock's Premier League
two to six
Unlight strikers taking against Locken
Locken one toss selected to field first
and they got the first wicket of Unlight
strikers very early
starting with two dot balls and then that
wicket fall of Madhav Kadam
Jayaraj strikes
Mahesh Shetty the new batsman
just going outside the stump line for a
wide first run in the account of Unlight
strikers
and that's a good strike in the air o the
fielder try to take that
good effort that will run away
for four runs Mahesh Shetty
first ball good strike
that could be the one more wicket fall but just a
fraction of a second
resulting in the boundary
change field settings directly new
fielder there at the corner mid wicket region
excellent bowling
the wicket keeper waiting was to hit on the
stumps but well saved Mahesh Shetty
Five balls five runs one wicket one
strikers
that's a good strike
excellent stop from Ramakrishnan they're going
for two runs
very good stop in the long off region wideish
long off fielder
1520 metres running for Ramakrishnan
so one gone 7 for one one strikers
Ramakrishnan is a bowling attack starting
with the wide
looking for the big one outside edge they are
looking for two runs
fielder standing at
deep backward point
and will take two runs here one on 10 that's
gone high in the air
and taken would you believe it
and is that the umpire will check
still checking the confirmation
and six runs given we thought
some time it will the catch been taken but no
after confirmation after checking
that's gone for six good strike
excellent running two runs taken would you believe it in that in
the throw they got that second run
two runs taken 18 for one
1.3 181
just a single
For that what was that we
thought the ball will go towards leg
side but going off side and four runs
unbelievable stuff this is
helicopter shot but off side region for four
runs
if you are watching on YouTube you will be really
surprised to watch this what was that
23 for one
16 runs of the over
so last ball coming up just
a single so 17 runs in the over and that is a
due factor will
bit of trouble in the field settings bit of
sloppy fielding so to go 24 for one
unlit strikers
so new bowler Dinesh Gurav
in the big attack
last over of the innings very good but only
single run last five
balls 25 for one
first over came 6 runs second over came 17
runs
and now third over in progress
this time it has been cut to make a place.  The ball is going towards the
deep backward point region.   We will have to be
satisfied with just one run.
A last four ball first innings on 26.
Mahesh Shetty is on strike
ball in the lock hole excellent stop there
dragging himself on the field
and the car will move forward with one run 27
last three balls in this first innings will
Devdas Rane go for a big fireworks already got that one
big hit at
long on
this time made room wanted to play but could
not time the
batsman misses keeper misses and one
by
last two balls 28 one
this time he has lifted the ball in the air fielder
is stationed there fumbling a bit two
runs going for the third run
and will be out two runs here will take two runs
and got out on the third run
last ball coming up of the first innings
last ball of the first innings they will
go for two for sure the throw and
that the strikers and they are going for one more
run
that's out
so two runs three was gone 32 for three
33 is a target to chase
I request for the coin tors for the
next match
Gallagher United
vs A on
match one winner vs match  Two winners Match One
winner Gallagher United Match Two winners
A on
First ball first blow
new batsman Ramakrishnan on non strike
Nitin
17 balls 33 runs
Radhakrishnan will face the next ball
right arm round the wicket very good ball
pulled on the on side
fielder present there.  We will have to be satisfied with just one run.
Now Nitin is on strike.
Nitin is a very good batsman.
Let's see whether he can make his team win or
not.   The
next ball was pushed gently with light hands towards the
off side and we had to be satisfied with a single run.
And a very good ball, a dot ball, the
fifth ball of this over was
completely beaten, a slightly
slow ball,
Ramakrishna could not understand, was
beaten by the pace of the ball,
wanted to hit it on the off side,
last ball of this over,
five balls, two runs, one wicket,
hit the ball on the off side, even though it was a misshot, it went
towards third man, had to be satisfied with one run,
one over,
three runs, 12 balls, 30 runs needed,
very
good bowling, gave only three runs in the power play
and one wicket,
second over of this match,
Ramakrishnan was on strike, it was a
good ball, was beaten again but
not only the batsman, the keeper was also beaten,
one run in the form of 22, umpire Naushad, leg
umpire Faya Sheikh,
one over, one ball, four runs, one wicket,
next ball, Nitin from the pavilion end,
right arm over the wicket, a very beautiful shot is to be
seen, player under the ball and could not stop it,
four runs on super cover,
Nitin
is a very good batsman at cover.  He
plays very well on the cover.
Third ball of this over: One over, two balls, eight
runs, one wicket.  Nitin is facing the next ball.   It was an
overpitched ball
which Nitin could not hit, he took a single off the inside edge of the leg.
Now Ramakrishnan
is a very high-rated player on strike.   The
bat lip also holds up.  I want to see this
ball.
Once again Ramashna was sitting.
Ramashannan being stumped,
one over, four balls, nine runs
and two wickets
to win, eight balls, 24 runs,
eight balls, 24 runs, the
fifth ball of this over is a good ball,
going out of good length, the batsman could
not understand it.  The keeper did the rest.   He is doing a
very intelligent
over.  There were three runs in the first over.
Six runs have been scored in this over so far.
Last ball of this over.   There was a
beat once more.
Very good bowling.
24 runs off six balls.
Now Nitin is on strike.
Let's hurry up a bit.
Last over of this match.
Right arm round the wicket.  First ball wide
ball.
23 runs off 6 balls,
tried to hit it on the leg side but again a
wide ball,
11 runs in two overs.   It was a
good ball.  Took a slight edge of the bat.   The
keeper could not stop him.
Total score: 2 overs, 1 ball, 12 runs, 2 wickets.
21 runs needed.
21 runs off five balls.
14 runs, two wickets,
four balls,
19 runs,
Dinesh strike,
shot hit on the off side, fielder sees it
under the ball,
Akshay did very good fielding, had to be satisfied with just one run,
now Nitin is on strike,
three balls, 18 runs, all three were long hits,
Akshay did very good fielding and
gave only one run, the
fielding side has completely taken control of this match
and once again got beaten,
four runs in extras on the last ball of this over,
won the match by 12 runs
and now listen to some good things from the
mouth of Mitesh ji in the com box.
Thank you very much Mr Om Singh you are very